sciweavers.org 2019-07-18

# Privacy | Sciweavers

This Privacy Policy covers sciweavers treatment of personal information that sciweavers gathers when you are on the sciweavers website and when you use sciweavers services.

## **PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION**

A user can use the entire website anonymously. However, he may prefer to create an account to access a custom service or feature such as add to favorites. During registration, users are asked to provide an email, username, and a password. We do not share the user email with any third party company. The email is used to communicate with the user whenever necessary. We adopt appropriate processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored on our Site. 

## **NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION**

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website through cookies. For example, basic demographic information, type of connecting device, operating system, Internet service providers, date and time of visit, referring URL, browser type, etc. The information we collect about your acitivity is not personal date and will remains anonymous. 

## **COOKIES**

This website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files stored in your browser which help us to understand how the website is used by you and hence be able to provide you with personalized, responsive, and great user experience. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the website. These companies may collect information about your visit to websites in order to provide advertisements that may be of interest to you. The IP address they collect is not personally identifiable. It can only identify your basic demographic information. Our third party advertisers include Google Adsense which may employ cookies on our site to serve ads. You may wish to visit Google Adsense for additional information about their privacy policies. Any user may opt out of Google's cookies by visiting: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Users can block or restrict cookies from the website through their internet browser settings. For more information please visit our Cookie Policy. 

## **E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS**

sciweavers is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party. sciweavers may send out e-mails with sciweavers-related news. You may also receive notification e-mails from sciweavers, which inform you of new page contents or comments you already subscribed on. If you do not want to receive notification e-mail from us, please unsubscribe. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices from us. 

## **CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your information, please contact us by admin@sciweavers.org or write to us at: 16228 Serenity Lane, Eden Prairie, MN, 55347 

## **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

sciweavers may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the sciweavers website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

## **YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

## **CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

In order to keep up with changing legislation and how we process your personal data, this Privacy Policy may be revised at any time without notice by posting an updated version on this website. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

## **EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 20 May 2018.
